[
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Ned Stark's sword?",
        "choices": [
            "Winter",
            "Ice",
            "Wolf's Tooth",
            "Longclaw"
        ],
        "answer": "Ice"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who has never been part of the Night's Watch?",
        "choices": [
            "Locke",
            "Mance Rayder",
            "Aemon Targaryen",
            "Orell"
        ],
        "answer": "Orell"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Sansa Stark's favorite treat?",
        "choices": [
            "Tyroshi pears",
            "Lamprey pie",
            "Lemon cakes",
            "Berry Tarts"
        ],
        "answer": "Lemon cakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who says, 'If we die, we die. But first, we'll live'?",
        "choices": [
            "Shae",
            "Tyrion Lannister",
            "Ygritte",
            "Bronn"
        ],
        "answer": "Ygritte"
    },
    {
        "question": "What signaled Khal Drogo's undefeated glory to the Dothraki?",
        "choices": [
            "The size of his Khalasar",
            "The length of his hair",
            "The Paint on his chest",
            "The number of his horses"
        ],
        "answer": "The length of his hair"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Bran Stark named after?",
        "choices": [
            "His Uncle",
            "His Grandfather",
            "His Cousin",
            "His Father"
        ],
        "answer": "His Uncle"
    },
    {
        "question": "What title does Jorah Mormont's father hold?",
        "choices": [
            "Hand of the King",
            "Lord Commander of the Kingsguard",
            "Lord Paramount of the Reach",
            "Lord Commander of the Night's Watch"
        ],
        "answer": "Lord Commander of the Night's Watch"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only thing Tywin Lannister believes lives on?",
        "choices": [
            "The Family Name",
            "The Family Honor",
            "The Family Gold",
            "The Family Glory"
        ],
        "answer": "The Family Name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who says, 'Nobody cares what your father once told you'?",
        "choices": [
            "Cersei Lannister",
            "Joffrey Baratheon",
            "Robert Baratheon",
            "Tyrion Lannister"
        ],
        "answer": "Cersei Lannister"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who Says, 'Chaos isn't a pit. It's a ladder'?",
        "choices": [
            "Varys",
            "Cersei Lannister",
            "Petyr Baelish",
            "Tyrion Lannister"
        ],
        "answer": "Petyr Baelish"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fill in the blank: 'What is _______ may never die.'",
        "choices": [
            "Dead",
            "Iron born",
            "Reborn",
            "Drowned "
        ],
        "answer": "Dead"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a Pirate?",
        "choices": [
            "Gendry",
            "Tycho Nestoris",
            "Salladhor Saan",
            "Mathos Seaworth"
        ],
        "answer": "Salladhor Saan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who saves Sansa Stark during the Riot of Kings Landing?",
        "choices": [
            "The Hound",
            "Tyrion lammister",
            "Joffrey Baratheon",
            "Perer baelish"
        ],
        "answer": ""
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of Danerys Targaryen's three Dragons are the largest?",
        "choices": [
            "Rhaegal",
            "Drogon",
            "Viserion",
            "Balerion"
        ],
        "answer": "Drogon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What caused the green fire at Blackwater bay?",
        "choices": [
            "Wildfire",
            "Napalm",
            "Greek fire",
            "Essence of Nightshade"
        ],
        "answer": "Wildfire"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who teaches Arya Stark to 'Stick'em with the pointy end'?",
        "choices": [
            "Syrio Forel",
            "Robb Stark",
            "Ned Stark",
            "Jon Snow"
        ],
        "answer": "Jon Snow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who HASN'T been the hand of the King?",
        "choices": [
            "Tyrion Lannister",
            "Jon Arryn",
            "Ned Stark",
            "Petyr Baelish"
        ],
        "answer": "Petyr Baelish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a Bastards lastname in Dorne?",
        "choices": [
            "Sand",
            "Storm",
            "Stone",
            "Dune"
        ],
        "answer": "Sand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who did Robb Stark promise to Marry in exchange for troops?",
        "choices": [
            "A Bolton Girl",
            "A Frey Girl",
            "A Baratheon Girl",
            "A Lannister Girl"
        ],
        "answer": "A Frey Girl"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Animal is on House Baratheon's Sigil?",
        "choices": [
            "Boar",
            "Bear",
            "Stag",
            "Wolf"
        ],
        "answer": "Stag"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Mad King to Daenerys Targaryen?",
        "choices": [
            "Her Father",
            "Her Brother",
            "Her Uncle",
            "Her Grandfather"
        ],
        "answer": "Her Father"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is NOT part of the Night's Watch vows?",
        "choices": [
            "Win no glory",
            "Take no wife",
            "Kill no Innocent",
            "Father no children"
        ],
        "answer": "Kill no Innocent"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are House Greyjoy's words?",
        "choices": [
            "We Remember",
            "We Guard the way",
            "We Pay the iron price",
            "We do not sow"
        ],
        "answer": "We do not sow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tyrion Lannister has a tender spot for bastards, cripples, and ________?",
        "choices": [
            "Children",
            "Imps",
            "Drunks",
            "Broken Things"
        ],
        "answer": "Broken Things"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are House Lannisters words?",
        "choices": [
            "A Lannister always pays his debts",
            "Ours be the Glory",
            "Hear me Roar!",
            "Righteous in Wrath"
        ],
        "answer": "Hear me Roar!"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who says, 'Of all the ways I'd kill you, poison would be the last'?",
        "choices": [
            "The Hound",
            "Cersei Lannister",
            "Mance Rayder",
            "Arya Stark"
        ],
        "answer": "Mance Rayder"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Father Legitimizes his bastard son?",
        "choices": [
            "Oberyn Martell",
            "Ned Stark",
            "Robert Baratheon",
            "Roose Bolton"
        ],
        "answer": "Roose Bolton"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is Melisandre from?",
        "choices": [
            "Asshai",
            "The Eyrie",
            "Dorne",
            "Highgarden"
        ],
        "answer": "Asshai"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Rickon's direworlf?",
        "choices": [
            "Shaggydog",
            "Wolf",
            "Summer",
            "Greywind"
        ],
        "answer": "Shaggydog"
    },
    {
        "question": "How does Robin Arryn want badmen to die?",
        "choices": [
            "By Fire",
            "By Decapitation",
            "By Poison",
            "By Moon door"
        ],
        "answer": "By Moon door"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was the last Targaryen in Westeros before Daenerys?",
        "choices": [
            "Casterly Rock",
            "King's Landing",
            "Castle Black",
            "Dorne"
        ],
        "answer": "Castle Black"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is sometimes reffered to as Ser Piggy or Prince Pork-Chop?",
        "choices": [
            "Jamie Lannister",
            "Theon Greyjoy",
            "Jon Snow",
            "Samwell Tarly"
        ],
        "answer": "Samwell Tarly"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who gives Robert Baratheon poisoned wine?",
        "choices": [
            "Lancel Lannister",
            "Cersei Lannister",
            "Jamie Lannister",
            "Petyr Baelish"
        ],
        "answer": "Lancel Lannister"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who does Oberyn Martell seek revenge for?",
        "choices": [
            "His Wife",
            "His Daughter",
            "His Sister",
            "His Mother"
        ],
        "answer": "His Sister"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who Says, 'You are no son of mine'?",
        "choices": [
            "Robert Baratheon",
            "Balon Greyjoy",
            "Catelyn Stark",
            "Tywin Lannister"
        ],
        "answer": "Tywin Lannister"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does 'dracarys' mean?",
        "choices": [
            "Burn",
            "Fly",
            "Kill",
            "Dragonfire"
        ],
        "answer": "Dragonfire"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT one of the Night's Watch Orders?",
        "choices": [
            "Guards",
            "Builders",
            "Stewards",
            "Rangers"
        ],
        "answer": "Guards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who cuts off Jamie Lannister's hand?",
        "choices": [
            "Rickard Karstark",
            "Roose Bolton",
            "Locke",
            "Polliver"
        ],
        "answer": "Locke"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where did Tyrion and Shae Meet?",
        "choices": [
            "The Eyrie",
            "Lannister Camp",
            "Kings Landing",
            "Brothel in the North"
        ],
        "answer": "Lannister Camp"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Kingdoms are in Westeros?",
        "choices": [
            "Two",
            "Six",
            "Seven",
            "Nine"
        ],
        "answer": "Seven"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fill in the blank: The night is dark and full of ________.",
        "choices": [
            "Tremmors",
            "Blood",
            "Terrors",
            "Evil"
        ],
        "answer": "Terrors"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Joffrey Baratheon's Valyrian steel blade?",
        "choices": [
            "Lion's Fang",
            "Dark Sister",
            "Hearteater",
            "Widow's Wail"
        ],
        "answer": "Widow's Wail"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Iron Bank?",
        "choices": [
            "Braavos",
            "Highgarden",
            "Pyke",
            "Dorne"
        ],
        "answer": "Braavos"
    },
    {
        "question": "What famous song played during the Red Wedding?",
        "choices": [
            "The Rains of Castamere ",
            "The Pains of Shastamere",
            "The bear and the Maiden fair",
            "Under the sea"
        ],
        "answer": "The Rains of Castamere "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is now a deadly poison?",
        "choices": [
            "Tears of lys",
            "Wolfsbane",
            "Essence of nightshade",
            "Milk of the poppy"
        ],
        "answer": "Milk of the poppy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does one horn blast mean for the Night's Watch?",
        "choices": [
            "Intruders",
            "Rangers Returning",
            "Rangers in trouble",
            "Spotted Wildlings"
        ],
        "answer": "Rangers Returning"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Daenerys Targaryen catapult across Mereen's walls?",
        "choices": [
            "Slave collars",
            "Hands",
            "Heads",
            "Broken Chains"
        ],
        "answer": "Broken Chains"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Tommen Baratheon's cat?",
        "choices": [
            "Ser Pounce",
            "Ser Meow",
            "Ser Whiskers",
            "Ser Paddington"
        ],
        "answer": "Ser Pounce"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is known as the Young Wolf?",
        "choices": [
            "Jon Snow",
            "Robb Stark",
            "Bran Stark",
            "Ned Stark"
        ],
        "answer": "Robb Stark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was going to be the Stalion who mounted the world?",
        "choices": [
            "Lyanna Stark's son",
            "Daenerys Targaryen's son",
            "Mance Rayder's son",
            "Robb Stark's son"
        ],
        "answer": "Daenerys Targaryen's son"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where does the red Wedding take place?",
        "choices": [
            "Riverrun",
            "The Red Keep",
            "The Twins",
            "The Eyrie"
        ],
        "answer": "The Twins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which House is supposedly 'first in battle'?",
        "choices": [
            "House Stark",
            "House Baratheon",
            "House Targaryen",
            "House Tarly"
        ],
        "answer": "House Tarly"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who Killed Jon Arryn?",
        "choices": [
            "Cersei Lannister",
            "Petyr Baelish",
            "Lysa Arryn",
            "Jamie Lannister"
        ],
        "answer": "Lysa Arryn"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the master of whisperers?",
        "choices": [
            "Tyrion Lannister",
            "Cersei Lannister",
            "Petyr Berlish",
            "Varys"
        ],
        "answer": "Varys"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Stark way is the _______ way.",
        "choices": [
            "Cold",
            "Gold",
            "Honorable",
            "Old"
        ],
        "answer": "Old"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which house is Petyr Baelish referring to when he says, 'Quick tempers, slow minds'?",
        "choices": [
            "House Stark",
            "House Lannister",
            "House Baratheon",
            "House Martell"
        ],
        "answer": "House Stark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who has Petyr Baelish loved since he was a child?",
        "choices": [
            "Sansa Stark",
            "Lysa Arryn",
            "Catelyn Stark",
            "Cersei Lannister"
        ],
        "answer": "Catelyn Stark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is NOT a face of 'the Seven'?",
        "choices": [
            "The Maiden",
            "The Widow",
            "The Mother",
            "The Stranger"
        ],
        "answer": "The Widow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Historically, Baratheon babies are born with what hair color?",
        "choices": [
            "Red",
            "Brown",
            "Yellow",
            "Black"
        ],
        "answer": "Black"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose execution does Bran Stark witness?",
        "choices": [
            "Gared",
            "Will",
            "Glenn",
            "Waymar"
        ],
        "answer": "Will"
    },
    {
        "question": "'Chaos isnt a pit, its a ladder' is a quote from? ",
        "choices": [
            "Varys",
            "Cersei Lannister",
            "Petyr Baelish",
            "Tyrion lannister"
        ],
        "answer": "Petyr Baelish"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who gives Daenerys Targaryen her dragon eggs? ",
        "choices": [
            "Jorah Mormont",
            "Illyrio Mopatis",
            "Viserys Targaryen",
            "Khal Drogo"
        ],
        "answer": "Illyrio Mopatis"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which season were all the Stark children born during?",
        "choices": [
            "Winter",
            "Spring",
            "Summer",
            "Fall"
        ],
        "answer": "Summer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Arya Stark's sword?",
        "choices": [
            "Icicle",
            "Nymeria",
            "Needle",
            "Pick"
        ],
        "answer": "Needle"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's Shireen Baratheon's Father?",
        "choices": [
            "Robert Baratheon",
            "Joffrey Baratheon",
            "Renly Baratheon",
            "Stannis Baratheon"
        ],
        "answer": "Stannis Baratheon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why does Ygritte say Mance Rayder will want to talk to Jon Snow?",
        "choices": [
            "Because Jon killed Qhorin Halfhand",
            "Because Jon's a crow",
            "Because of Jon Starks Blood",
            "Because Jon is a deserter"
        ],
        "answer": "Because of Jon Starks Blood"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Arya Starks Sword?",
        "choices": [
            "Nymeria",
            "Needle",
            "Lion's Bane",
            "Prick"
        ],
        "answer": "Needle"
    },
    {
        "question": "After Renly Baratheon dies, who do most of this bannermen submit to?",
        "choices": [
            "Robert Baratheon",
            "Joffrey Baratheon",
            "Robb Stark",
            "Stannis Baratheon"
        ],
        "answer": "Stannis Baratheon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do the Wildlings call those living south of the wall?",
        "choices": [
            "Sheep",
            "Kneelers",
            "Followers",
            "Cowards"
        ],
        "answer": "Kneelers"
    },
    {
        "question": "What can defenitley kill a White Walker?",
        "choices": [
            "Iron",
            "Sunlight",
            "Dragon Fire",
            "Dragon Glass"
        ],
        "answer": "Dragon Glass"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who has Margaery Tyrell NOT been bethrothed to?",
        "choices": [
            "Tommen Baratheon",
            "Renly Baratheon",
            "Stannis Baratheon",
            "Joffrey Baratheon"
        ],
        "answer": "Stannis Baratheon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Ned Stark tell Bran when he beheads a deserter in the pilot episode?",
        "choices": [
            "Our way is the old way",
            "All men must die",
            "Fear cuts deeper than a sword",
            "Winter is coming"
        ],
        "answer": "Our way is the old way"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the first character to say the phrase 'Game of Thrones'?",
        "choices": [
            "Tywin Lannister",
            "Cersei Lannister",
            "Tyrion Lannister",
            "Petyr Baelish"
        ],
        "answer": "Cersei Lannister"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Daenerys Targaryen to Jon Snow?",
        "choices": [
            "His Aunt",
            "His Woman",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Mountain is the nickname for which character?",
        "choices": [
            "Gerald Clegane",
            "Oberyn Martell",
            "Sandor Clegane",
            "Gregor Clegane"
        ],
        "answer": "Gregor Clegane"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is lord Commander of the Kingsguard at the beginning of Game of Thrones?",
        "choices": [
            "Ser Jamie Lannister",
            "Ser Barristan Selmy",
            "Ser Jeor Mormont",
            "Ser Loras Tyrell"
        ],
        "answer": "Ser Barristan Selmy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was Margaery Tyrell's first husband?",
        "choices": [
            "Renly Baratheon",
            "Joffrey Baratheon",
            "Stannis Baratheon",
            "Tommen Baratheon"
        ],
        "answer": "Renly Baratheon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is known as 'The King Beyond the Wall'",
        "choices": [
            "Tormund Giantsbane",
            "Mance Rayder",
            "The Night King",
            "Stannis Baratheon"
        ],
        "answer": ""
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times has Sansa Stark been married?",
        "choices": [
            "Twice",
            "Once",
            "Three times",
            "Four times"
        ],
        "answer": "Twice"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the Mad Kings firstborn son?",
        "choices": [
            "Aemon Targaryen",
            "Aegon Targaryen",
            "Rhaegar Targaryen",
            "Viserys Targaryen"
        ],
        "answer": "Rhaegar Targaryen"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who delivered the fatal blow to the King in the North Robb Stark?",
        "choices": [
            "Alliser Thorne",
            "Roose Bolton",
            "Ramsay Bolton",
            "Walder Frey"
        ],
        "answer": "Roose Bolton"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city does Samwell Tarly travel to in order to train as a maester?",
        "choices": [
            "Sunspear",
            "Highgarden",
            "Gulltown",
            "Oldtown"
        ],
        "answer": "Oldtown"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city does Arya Stark train to become a Faceless man?",
        "choices": [
            "Meereen",
            "Pentos",
            "Astapor",
            "Braavos"
        ],
        "answer": "Braavos"
    }
]